Guide to the United Brewery Workers records, 1888-1977 IBT0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
United Brewery Workers Records
1888-2004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Feller, Karl
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers of America. Convention
IBT0003
16.5 Linear Feet
This collection consists of material relating to the United Brewery Workers Union. Included are historical material, convention proceedings, General Executive Board minutes and general correspondence microfilm, and newspapers. These range in date from 1888-1977.
Arrangement
Organized into six series: Historical Materials, Convention Materials, General Executive Board Session Materials, General Correspondence Microfilm, The Brewery Worker newspaper and materials relating to Local 222.
Scope and Contents
The United Brewery Workers Records consists of convention proceedings, Officers' and Presidents' reports, General Executive Board minutes, miscellaneous printed matter and general correspondence microfilm. The materials range in date from 1888-1977.
Biographical / Historical
In 1973, after many years of sometimes violent jurisdictional disputes with the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), the International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America merged with its arch-rival, becoming the Brewery and Soft Drink Conference of the IBT. Founded in 1886 as the National Union of Brewery Workmen, the union was largely composed of German immigrants. Its convention proceedings and publications were printed in German until 1903 and bilingually until 1917.
Affiliated with the American Federation of Labor (AFL) from the time of its founding, the United Brewery Workers Union withdrew from the AFL in 1946 to affiliate with the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO). A particularly violent series of jurisdictional battles between the United Brewery Workers and the Teamsters took place in Pittsburgh in 1946 which included strikes, picket lines, street fights and lawsuits. What became known as the "Pittsburgh Beer War" was the subject of a Congressional investigation in 1947.
The decision to merge with the Teamsters stemmed from the closing of hundreds of local breweries in the 1950s and 1960s as well as the expanded competition with large national brewers such as Anheuser-Busch. Due to the numerous name changes the union undertook over the years and to the length of its name at the time of the merger, the collection is referred to as The United Brewery Workers Records.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2/1/2011 (2011.049) and 11/15/2014 (2014.042).
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Conferences; Labor; Labor unions; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers of America. Convention
- Historical Materials, 1917-1973; Series 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of historic material relating to the United Brewery Workers. These range in date from 1917-1960. Included is the Brewery Worker's Constitution and legal documents.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Circulation letter, 1917; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, 1926; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence regarding affiliation between The International Union of United Brewery Workers and AFL-CIO, September 24, 1973; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - International Union of Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers La Crosse Company Announcements, 1920; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - International Union of Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers La Crosse Company Announcements, 1920-1921; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Legal documents: Brewery vs Carl Becherer, appendix to petition, 1949; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Legal documents: Brewery vs Carl Becherer, appendix to brief, 1949; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Legal documents: Brewery vs Carl Becherer, petitions and briefs, 1949; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Report: Problems and Prospects by Leon H. Keyserling, 1960 September; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Trend Toward Merger is Accelerating Among Labor Unions," The New York Times, December 20, 1972; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Convention Materials, 1888-1973; Series 2; 5 Linear Feet
  This series consists of material relating to the United Brewery Workers annual conventions dating from 1888-1973. Included are official proceedings, minutes and President and Officer's reports.
  Organized into three subseries: Official proceedings, Minutes, and President and Officer's reports.
  - Official proceedings, 1888-1973; Series 2 Subseries 1; 2.5 Linear Feet
    Arranged chronologically
    This subseries contains offical proceedings of the United Brewery Workers conventions dating from 1888-1973. Material covered within these proceedings include lists of delegates, session activities, orders and resolutions, auditing committee statistics and rules of order.
    - Proceedings of the 3rd convention, 1888; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the 4th convention, 1889; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 5th convention, 1891; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the 7th convention, 1893; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the 9th convention, 1896; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the 10th convention, 1897; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the 11th convention, 1899; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Proceedings of the 12th convention, 1900; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings of the 13th convention, 1901; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings of the 14th convention, 1903; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Proceedings of the 15th-17th conventions, 1904-1908; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the 18th, 19th conventions, 1910-1912; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 20th convention, 1914; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the 21st convention, 1917; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the 22th convention, 1920; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 23rd convention, 1923; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the 24th convention, 1926; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the 25th convention, 1933; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the 26th convention, 1936; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the 27th convention, 1939; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Proceedings of the 28th convention, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings of the 29th convention, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings of the 30th convention, 1948 September 13-18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the 31st convention, 1950 September 11-15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 32nd convention, 1952 July 14-18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the 33rd convention, 1954 September 13-17; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the 34th convention, 1956 August 13-17; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the 35th convention, 1959 August; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the 36th convention, 1961 August; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the 37th convention, 1963 August 12-15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 38th convention, 1965 October 4-7; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the 39th convention, 1968 August 12-15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the 40th convention, 1971 September 27-30; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the special convention, 1973 November 5-6; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1952-1971; Series 2 Subseries 2; 1.5 Linear Feet
    This subseries comprises of stenotyped records of the United Brewery Workers conventions dating from 1952-1971. They contain detailed descriptions of the the events of the conventions, announcements and reports by the Constitution Committee and the Resolutions Committee.
    - Minutes of the 32nd convention, volume V, 1952 July 18; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of the 33rd convention, volume I, 1954 September 13; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the 33rd convention, volume II, 1954 September 14; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of the 33rd convention, volume III, 1954 September 15; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of the 33rd convention, volume IV, 1954 September 16; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the 33rd convention, volume V, 1954 September 17; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of the 35th convention, volume I, 1959 August 10; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of the 35th convention, volume II, 1959 August 11; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the 35th convention, volume III, 1959 August 10-13; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of the 35th convention, volume IV, 1959 August 13; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of the 36th convention, volume I, 1961 August 14; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the 36th convention, volume II, 1961 August 15; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of the 36th convention, volume III, 1961 August 16; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of the 39th convention, volume I, 1968 August 12; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of the 39th convention, volume II, 1968 August 13; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the 39th convention, volume III, 1968 August 14; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of the 39th convention, volume IV, 1968 August 15; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of the 40th convention, volume I, 1971 September 27; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the 40th convention, volume II, 1971 September 28; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of the 40th convention, volume III, 1971 September 29; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of the 40th convention, volume IV, 1971 September 30; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - President and Officers reports, 1917-1971; Series 2 Subseries 3; 1 Linear Feet
    This subseries, dating from 1917-1971, contains the President's and Officer's reports presented at the United Brewery Workers conventions. Issues covered within the reports include reviews of events, statistics and graphs of sales production, information on strikes, selling trends and average wages.
    - Officer's report at the 21st convention, 1917 December 3; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Officer's report at the 24th convention, 1926 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Officer's report at the 25th convention, 1933 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Officer's report at the 26th convention, 1936 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Officer's report at the 27th convention, 1939 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Officer's report at the 28th convention, 1942 September; Series 2 Subseries 3; 0.5 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Officer's report at the 29th convention, 1946 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Officer's report at the 30th convention, 1948 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Officer's report at the 31th convention, 1950 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - President's report at the 32nd convention, 1952 July; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - President's report at the 33rd convention, 1954 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - President's report at the 34th convention, 1956 August; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - President's report at the 35th convention, 1959 August; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - President's report at the 36th convention, 1961 August; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - President's report at the 39th convention, 1968 August; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - President's report at the 40th convention, 1971 September; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Session Materials, 1947-1977; Series 3; 6 Linear Feet
  Organized into two subseries: Minutes and Session mailers.
  This series consists of material relating to the United Brewery Workers General Executive Board sessions dating from 1947-1977. Included are session minutes and mailers.
  - Minutes, 1914-1977; Series 3 Subseries 1; 4.5 Linear Feet
    The material in this subseries contains the recorded minutes of the General Executive Board sessions dating from 1935-1970. The minutes detail the proceedings of the sessions including information regarding reports given, contracts endorsed and elections held.
    - Executive Meeting Minutes Book, 1914-1920 (Box 23, Item 1)
    - Executive Meeting Minutes Book, 1922 June 21 - 1924 January 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Executive Meeting Minutes Book, 1928 October 9 - 1931 February 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1935 January - 1942 December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1938 July - 1939 May; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1938 December - 1939 May; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1939 June - July; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1939 August - September; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1939 October - November; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1939 December - 1940 February; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1940 March - May; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1940 June - August; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1940 September - October; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1940 November - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1941 January - February; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 1941 March - April; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1941 May; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1941 December - 1942 January; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1942 February; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1942 March; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1942 April; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1942 May; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1942 June; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1942 July; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1942 August - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1943 January; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1943 February - March; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1943 April - May; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 1943 June; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1943 July - August; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1943 September - November; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1945 January - 1946 June; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1946 April - 1947 June; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1947 January 2 - 1947 December 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1948 January 7 - 1948 December 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1949 January 7 - 1949 December 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1951 January 8 - 1952 December 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1953 January 12 - 1954 December 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1955 January 24 - 1956 December 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1957 January 23 - 1958 December 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1959 January - December, 1960 January - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1961 January - December, 1961 January - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1962 January - December, 1962 January - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1963 January - December, 1964 January - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1965 January - December, 1969 January - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1970 January - December, 1973 January - December; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Session mailers, 1941-1947; Series 3 Subseries 2; 2.5 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains mailers and proofs of the sessions of the General Executive Board dating from 1941-1947. These records chornicle the events of the General Executive Board sessions and were mailed to members of the United Brewery Workers union.
    - Session proofs, 1941 January-September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Session proofs, 1941 October - December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Session proofs, 1942 September - December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Session proofs, 1945 June - July; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Session proofs, 1945 August - September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Session proofs, 1945 October - November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Session proofs, 1945 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Session proofs, 1946 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Session proofs, 1946 February - March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Session proofs, 1946 April - May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Session proofs, 1946 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Session proofs, 1946 July - August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Session proofs, 1946 September - October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Session proofs, 1946 November - December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Session proofs, 1947 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Session Mailer, 1940 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Session Mailer, 1940 September - November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Session Mailer, 1940 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Session Mailer, 1941 March - April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Session mailers, 1941 January - October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Session Mailer, 1941 January - February; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Session mailers, 1941 October - December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Session Mailer, 1941 December - 1942 February; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Session Mailer, 1942 April - May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Session Mailer, 1942 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Session Mailer, 1942 July - August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Session Mailer, 1942 November - January 1943; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Session mailers, 1942 September - November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Session Mailer, 1943 February - March; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Session Mailer, 1943 April; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Session Mailer, 1943 April - June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Session Mailer, 1943 July - August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Session Mailer, 1943 September - October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Session mailers, 1945 June - July; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Session mailers, 1945 August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Session mailers, 1945 September; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Session mailers, 1945 October - November; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Session mailers, 1945 December; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Session mailers, 1946 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Session mailers, 1946 February - May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Session mailers, 1946 April - May; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Session mailers, 1946 June; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Session mailers, 1946 July - August; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Session mailers, 1946 September - October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Session mailers, 1946 November - 1947 January; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence Microfilm, 1911-1947; Series 4
  Arranged by Local Union number.
  This series consists of material relating to the United Brewery Workers general correspondence in microfilm form. The reels range in date from 1911-1947. Most, however, are from the 1930s and 1940s. Many Local Unions have more than one reel concerning their undertakings.
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #71, 1936 December 21; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 29)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #77, 1944 December 19 (Box 19, Reel 29)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #77, 1937 December 18; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 29)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #77, 1930 December 9; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 29)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #78, 1934 June 6; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 29)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #79, 1947 December 16; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 30)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #79, 1939 December 10; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 30)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #80, 1947 January 17; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 30)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #81, 1947 December 30; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 30)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #81, 1944 January 7; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 30)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #81, 1943 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 31)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #81, 1936 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 31)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #82, 1940 August; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 31)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #84, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 31)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #84, 1936 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 31)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #84, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 32)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #85, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 32)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #85, 1940 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 32)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #85, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 32)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #85, 1939 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 33)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #85, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 33)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #85, 1911 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 33)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #85- Ben Love Case, 1932 November; 1939 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 34)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #85- Ben Love Case, 1932 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 34)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #87, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 35)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #90, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 35)